TIMOTIUS DWI YULIANTO MALAU

xii8a.timotiusdym20@gmail.com | linkedin.com/timotius-dwi-yulianto-malau | github.com/timotiusdwiyuliantomalau

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

An undergraduate student of Informatic and Computer Engineer Education who is passionate in Web Development. Is a responsible person, hardworking person, want to learn new thing and well communicative. Actively, create some project website using many tech stack. I am ready to be part in this company and growing more for future experience

EXPERIENCE

Kampus Mengajar Batch 4

Feb 2023 - June 2023

- Taking part in technology needs
- · Create information system of school library in there school
- · Lead sustainability of online assessment

Independent Study (Data Analyst)

Aug 2023 - Dec 2023

- Learning processing data by study case that given
- Visualizationing data based on data processed
- Complete team project by using all knowledge and tools learned

EDUCATION

Universitas Negeri Semarang - Semarang City, Indonesia

Aug 2020 - Aug 2024

Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering Bachelor's Degree, 3.57/4.00

BNSP's Certification of Junior Web Developer

Aug 2024

As a sign that the participant has proper to working in industry

PORTOFOLIO

Tiktok Clone Web

is a clone of Tiktok, which this plaform could share expression via videos.

E-Commerce

is a website for do shopping items untill payment

Generator of Multiple Choice Question

is a platform for teachers could generate many question by inputing learning objective

Movie Ticket Purchasing Web

is a web for find out which films are currently showing, search for the film you want, and buy film tickets

Resto App Mobile

ORGANIZATION

Creating an application for food ordering and delivery.

Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

Christian Spiritual Unit - Member of Misi Departement

Christian Spiritual Unit is a college activity unit which arrange sustanability christian activity in UNNES.

- Register new christian student college in UNNES ya
- · Reach out new christian student college and inviting them to join in christian spritual unit's activity
- Being the supporter for new christian student college if them need a hand

SKILLS

- Hard skill: Javascipt, NextJS, PHP, Laravel, NodeJS, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase
- Soft skill: Team working, responsible person, well communicate, and determined to learn new thing
- Languages: Indonesia, English (Intermediate)